"use strict";(self.webpackChunkquiz_app=self.webpackChunkquiz_app||[]).push([[982],{3982:e=>{e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"question":"What is AWS Organizations?","answers":[{"text":"A service for organizing physical events","isCorrect":false},{"text":"A service for creating and managing AWS accounts","isCorrect":true},{"text":"A service for managing DNS records","isCorrect":false},{"text":"A service for automating software deployment","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the primary benefit of using AWS Organizations?","answers":[{"text":"Increased network speed","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Centralized billing and cost management","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Enhanced security of data at rest","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Improved application performance","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the structure used by AWS Organizations to organize accounts?","answers":[{"text":"Regions","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Domains","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Organizational Units (OUs) and accounts","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Security groups","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"How can you invite existing AWS accounts to join an AWS Organization?","answers":[{"text":"By sending a physical invitation letter","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By using AWS CloudFormation templates","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By sending an email invitation","isCorrect":true},{"text":"By updating DNS records","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is an Organizational Unit (OU) in AWS Organizations?","answers":[{"text":"A unit of storage in Amazon S3","isCorrect":false},{"text":"A group of accounts within an organization","isCorrect":true},{"text":"A virtual machine in the AWS Cloud","isCorrect":false},{"text":"A domain name registered with AWS Route 53","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the purpose of Service Control Policies (SCPs) in AWS Organizations?","answers":[{"text":"To control access to Amazon S3 buckets","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To manage IAM roles for EC2 instances","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To set fine-grained permissions on AWS accounts within an organization","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To configure VPC settings","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"How can you apply a Service Control Policy (SCP) to an Organizational Unit (OU) in AWS Organizations?","answers":[{"text":"By directly attaching it to IAM users","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By associating it with a specific AWS region","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By attaching it to the root of the organization","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By attaching it to the OU or an account","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the AWS Organization Root?","answers":[{"text":"The root domain of a website hosted on AWS","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The top-level entity in an AWS Organization hierarchy","isCorrect":true},{"text":"A special IAM user created by AWS Organizations","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The main virtual machine in a VPC","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"How can you move an AWS account from one Organizational Unit (OU) to another?","answers":[{"text":"By creating a new AWS account","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By using AWS CLI only","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By updating DNS records","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By using the AWS Management Console or AWS CLI","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the AWS Organizations policy type that specifies the maximum and minimum AWS regions that accounts can use?","answers":[{"text":"IAM Policy","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Service Control Policy (SCP)","isCorrect":true},{"text":"VPC Policy","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Amazon S3 Bucket Policy","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the AWS resource type targeted by AWS Organizations policies?","answers":[{"text":"IAM Users","isCorrect":false},{"text":"AWS EC2 instances","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Organizational Units (OUs)","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Amazon S3 buckets","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"How can you enforce an AWS Organizations policy across your entire organization?","answers":[{"text":"By attaching it to a specific region only","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By creating a new AWS account","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By attaching it to the root of the organization","isCorrect":true},{"text":"By applying it only to IAM users","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the purpose of the AWS Organization ID?","answers":[{"text":"To identify IAM users","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To encrypt data at rest","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To uniquely identify an AWS organization","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To configure network security groups","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the maximum number of AWS accounts allowed in an AWS organization?","answers":[{"text":"Unlimited","isCorrect":true},{"text":"10","isCorrect":false},{"text":"5","isCorrect":false},{"text":"20","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the purpose of the AWS Consolidated Billing feature in AWS Organizations?","answers":[{"text":"To consolidate AWS regions for billing purposes","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To consolidate multiple AWS accounts for billing purposes","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To consolidate billing for AWS and non-AWS services","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To consolidate billing for EC2 instances only","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"How does AWS Consolidated Billing affect the payment of bills?","answers":[{"text":"It does not affect billing","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Each account pays its own bill separately","isCorrect":false},{"text":"It combines the bills of all accounts into a single payment","isCorrect":true},{"text":"It only consolidates bills for specific services","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the AWS resource type used for grouping accounts for billing purposes in AWS Organizations?","answers":[{"text":"Organizational Units (OUs)","isCorrect":false},{"text":"IAM Roles","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Linked accounts","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Consolidated Billing accounts","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the benefit of using AWS Control Tower in conjunction with AWS Organizations?","answers":[{"text":"To control access to Amazon S3 buckets","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To simplify the process of setting up and governing a secure, multi-account AWS environment","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To manage IAM users for an organization","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To automate software deployment","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"How can you disable an AWS account within an AWS Organization?","answers":[{"text":"By terminating all EC2 instances","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By removing the account from the organization","isCorrect":true},{"text":"By deleting the IAM user associated with the account","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By disabling the AWS CLI access","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the purpose of AWS Single Sign-On (SSO) in the context of AWS Organizations?","answers":[{"text":"To manage DNS records","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To enable centralized access control to AWS accounts","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To manage AWS resources","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To configure VPC settings","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"How can you use AWS Organizations to simplify the billing for multiple accounts?","answers":[{"text":"By creating separate AWS accounts for each department","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By manually consolidating bills using the AWS Management Console","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By enabling AWS Consolidated Billing","isCorrect":true},{"text":"By associating accounts with IAM roles","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the AWS Organizations feature that helps detect and prevent unused or underutilized accounts?","answers":[{"text":"Service Control Policies (SCPs)","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Organizational Units (OUs)","isCorrect":false},{"text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Consolidated Billing","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the purpose of AWS Organizations Audit Manager?","answers":[{"text":"To manage IAM roles","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To audit and assess the operational and security risks of your AWS environment","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To initiate archive retrieval jobs in Amazon Glacier","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To configure VPC settings","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"How can you use AWS Organizations to apply consistent tagging across multiple accounts?","answers":[{"text":"By manually updating tags for each resource in every account","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By using AWS CLI only","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By using AWS Resource Groups","isCorrect":true},{"text":"By creating separate AWS accounts for each tag","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the AWS Organizations feature that helps you automate the creation of new accounts based on pre-approved templates?","answers":[{"text":"AWS CloudTrail","isCorrect":false},{"text":"AWS Control Tower","isCorrect":true},{"text":"AWS Organizations Policy","isCorrect":false},{"text":"AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) Roles","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is AWS Control Tower?","answers":[{"text":"A service for controlling access to Amazon S3 buckets","isCorrect":false},{"text":"A service for controlling access to EC2 instances","isCorrect":false},{"text":"A service for setting up and governing a secure, multi-account AWS environment","isCorrect":true},{"text":"A service for managing DNS records","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is AWS Service Catalog in the context of AWS Organizations?","answers":[{"text":"A service for cataloging physical items","isCorrect":false},{"text":"A service for managing DNS records","isCorrect":false},{"text":"A service for creating, managing, and distributing catalogs of approved products","isCorrect":true},{"text":"A service for managing IAM roles","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"How can you use AWS Organizations to enforce tagging compliance across accounts?","answers":[{"text":"By relying on individual account owners to enforce tagging","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By manually reviewing tags periodically","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By using AWS Config rules and AWS Organizations Service Control Policies (SCPs)","isCorrect":true},{"text":"By disabling tagging for all resources","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the purpose of AWS Organizations service-linked roles?","answers":[{"text":"To manage IAM users","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To enable centralized access control","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To configure VPC settings","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To initiate archive retrieval jobs in Amazon Glacier","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"How can you move an AWS account from one organization to another?","answers":[{"text":"It\'s not possible","isCorrect":true},{"text":"By using the AWS Organizations console","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By contacting AWS support","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By updating the account settings","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the purpose of service control policies (SCPs) in AWS Organizations?","answers":[{"text":"To manage IAM users","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To enable centralized access control","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To set fine-grained permissions on AWS accounts within an organization","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To configure VPC settings","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"Which AWS service is integrated with AWS Organizations to enable consolidated billing?","answers":[{"text":"Amazon S3","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Amazon EC2","isCorrect":false},{"text":"AWS Billing and Cost Management","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Amazon RDS","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"How can you create a new organizational unit (OU) in AWS Organizations?","answers":[{"text":"Through the AWS Management Console","isCorrect":true},{"text":"By using AWS CLI commands","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By sending an API request to AWS Organizations","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By contacting AWS support","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the purpose of an organizational unit (OU) in AWS Organizations?","answers":[{"text":"To create IAM users","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To define VPC configurations","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To group AWS accounts within an organization","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To configure AWS Config rules","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"How can you enable or disable AWS accounts within an organizational unit (OU)?","answers":[{"text":"By updating individual account settings","isCorrect":false},{"text":"By using AWS CLI commands","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Through the AWS Management Console","isCorrect":true},{"text":"By contacting AWS support","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the benefit of using AWS Organizations for managing multiple AWS accounts?","answers":[{"text":"To increase the performance of individual accounts","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To consolidate billing and cost management","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To configure security groups","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To create IAM users","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"How can you apply service control policies (SCPs) in AWS Organizations?","answers":[{"text":"To individual AWS accounts","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To IAM roles","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To organizational units (OUs) and AWS accounts","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To Amazon S3 buckets","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What happens to AWS accounts when they are removed from an organization in AWS Organizations?","answers":[{"text":"They are permanently deleted","isCorrect":false},{"text":"They become independent standalone accounts","isCorrect":true},{"text":"They lose access to all AWS services","isCorrect":false},{"text":"They are moved to a suspended state","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"Which AWS service allows you to view and manage your AWS bills for multiple accounts?","answers":[{"text":"AWS Cost Explorer","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Amazon RDS","isCorrect":false},{"text":"AWS Billing and Cost Management","isCorrect":true},{"text":"AWS Config","isCorrect":false}]}]')}}]);